Manage deployments

Usage: railway.exe deployment <COMMAND>

Commands:
  list      List deployments for a service with IDs, statuses and other metadata
  up        Upload and deploy project from the current directory
  redeploy  Redeploy the latest deployment of a service
  help      Print this message or the help of the given subcommand(s)

Options:
  -h, --help     Print help
  -V, --version  Print version

